{
  "numberTest": [
    {
      "question": "Զրո",
      "variant1": "1",
      "variant2": "5",
      "variant3": "0",
      "variant4": "8",
      "right": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Հինգ",
      "variant1": "6",
      "variant2": "0",
      "variant3": "3",
      "variant4": "5",
      "right": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Երկու",
      "variant1": "2",
      "variant2": "7",
      "variant3": "3",
      "variant4": "8",
      "right": "1"
    }
  ],
  "abcTest": [
    {
      "question": "Ա",
      "variant1": "Vo",
      "variant2": "A",
      "variant3": "N",
      "variant4": "P",
      "right": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Կ",
      "variant1": "T",
      "variant2": "Ye",
      "variant3": "U",
      "variant4": "K",
      "right": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Զ",
      "variant1": "Z",
      "variant2": "Yev",
      "variant3": "Vo",
      "variant4": "F",
      "right": "1"
    }
  ],
  "communicationTest": [
    {
      "question": "Բարև",
      "variant1": "hello",
      "variant2": "how are you?",
      "variant3": "bye",
      "variant4": "thank you",
      "right": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "ցտեսություն",
      "variant1": "bye",
      "variant2": "please",
      "variant3": "hi",
      "variant4": "how are you?",
      "right": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ինչպե՞ս ես",
      "variant1": "no",
      "variant2": "how are you?",
      "variant3": "thank you",
      "variant4": "bye",
      "right": "2"
    }
  ],
  "colorTest": [
    {
      "question": "Կարմիր",
      "variant1": "red",
      "variant2": "green",
      "variant3": "blue",
      "variant4": "white",
      "right": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Կապույտ",
      "variant1": "yellow",
      "variant2": "blue",
      "variant3": "white",
      "variant4": "brown",
      "right": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Նարնջագույն",
      "variant1": "orange",
      "variant2": "yellow",
      "variant3": "white",
      "variant4": "red",
      "right": "1"
    }
  ],
  "foodTest": [
    {
      "question": "ջուր",
      "variant1": "egg",
      "variant2": "bread",
      "variant3": "water",
      "variant4": "grass",
      "right": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "ձու",
      "variant1": "egg",
      "variant2": "grass",
      "variant3": "water",
      "variant4": "bread",
      "right": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "հաց",
      "variant1": "bread",
      "variant2": "water",
      "variant3": "grass",
      "variant4": "egg",
      "right": "1"
    }
  ],
  "natureTest": [
    {
      "question": "ամպ",
      "variant1": "cloud",
      "variant2": "tree",
      "variant3": "cat",
      "variant4": "grass",
      "right": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "կատու",
      "variant1": "cat",
      "variant2": "grass",
      "variant3": "cloud",
      "variant4": "tree",
      "right": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "խոտ",
      "variant1": "tree",
      "variant2": "cat",
      "variant3": "grass",
      "variant4": "cloud",
      "right": "3"
    }
  ]
}